<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Welcome to my Portfolio! on Doudmine</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/</link><description>Recent content in Welcome to my Portfolio! on Doudmine</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.doudmine.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My portfoio website</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/portfolio/project-2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/portfolio/project-2/</guid><description>Project Details When I first decided to create my personal website, I experimented with a lot of options and spent a significant amount of time learning Gatsby and trying various templates. But I didn&amp;rsquo;t feel I could achieve what I wanted with free templates, In addition I found it complicated because I&amp;rsquo;m not familiar with React. I also didn&amp;rsquo;t want to worry about resolving issues every time I wanted to tweak something, so I went with Hugo, which only requires a basic understanding of HTML, CSS, and JS.</description></item><item><title>Cosmetic Landing page - Shopify</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/portfolio/project-1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2021 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/portfolio/project-1/</guid><description>Project Details The development of a simple landing page for practicing Shopify liquid. It is based on a design that I found on dribbble by Syed Roni, I developed it from scratch using HTML, CSS, JS, GULP and LIQUID.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/page/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/page/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Project 1 - landing page</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/page/project1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/page/project1/</guid><description>Project 1 - Hugo ships with several Built-in Shortcodes for rich content, along with a Privacy Config and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.</description></item><item><title>Project 2 - landing page</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/page/project2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/page/project2/</guid><description>Project 2 - Hugo ships with several Built-in Shortcodes for rich content, along with a Privacy Config and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.</description></item><item><title>Custom Header With Hide on Scroll Down &amp; Show on Scroll Up</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/custom-navigation-header/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/custom-navigation-header/</guid><description>Have you ever wondered if it&amp;rsquo;s possible to customize the header of your Shopify store to something more robust and professional, the answer is big yes! That&amp;rsquo;s what we are going to see in this article tutorial. Also I encourage you to watch the whole video on YouTube, so you can use this custom header easily and If you are not using Minimal theme and you want this header on your Shopify store then DM me on Instagram so I can create it for you.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Slider for your Shopify store</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/advanced-slider/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/advanced-slider/</guid><description>Product Sliders allows showing all suggested products friendly that match to customer’s expectation via a responsive slider. This product slider you&amp;rsquo;re going to see is full of advanced features such as sale and sold out badges also change product picture on hover effect and more! so if you like this tutorial please share it with your friends. so let&amp;rsquo;s get started
From your Shopify admin, go to Online Store &amp;gt; Themes.</description></item><item><title>How to add the Parallax section in your Shopify</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/parallax-section/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/parallax-section/</guid><description>In this tutorial article we will be adding a parallax section with fixed scrolling using HTML and CSS and LIQUID. You will see that when you scroll the image inside the section will stay in place, so let me show you how to add it to your Shopify store.
From your Shopify admin, go to Online Store &amp;gt; Themes. Find the Minimal theme, and then click Actions &amp;gt; Duplicate. Find the theme that called Copy of Minimal then click Actions &amp;gt; Edit Code.</description></item><item><title>Customize &amp; add product badges</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/customize-product-badges/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/customize-product-badges/</guid><description>There are many ways to attach visitor’s attention to a product. One of the most popular ways is by adding a small badge, usually on the top left or right corner of the product image. In this article I&amp;rsquo;m going to show you how to create a simple NEW and HOT icon badge for a product with the help of Metafields and also how to customize the Sale &amp;amp; Soldout badge in the Minimal theme, so let&amp;rsquo;s get started!</description></item><item><title>Products carousel slider for Shopify</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/products-carousel-slider-for-shopify/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/products-carousel-slider-for-shopify/</guid><description>Product Sliders allows showing all suggested products friendly that match to customer’s expectation via a responsive slider. You can create many product sliders as featured, bestsellers, new arrival products or anything else that you want your customers to see in your store. Also you can create many product sliders that you want to attract customers to make a purchase from your website without any apps, so let me show you step by step</description></item><item><title>Displaying custom author names using custom fields</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/displaying-custom-author-names/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/displaying-custom-author-names/</guid><description>By default, Shopify themes will display a blog post author based on staff admin accounts but it’s possible to edit the article template and display any author name you would like with the help of custom fields. So let me show you how to feature a guest blogger who you would like to credit as the author
From your Shopify admin, go to Online Store &amp;gt; Themes. Find the Minimal theme, and then click Actions &amp;gt; Duplicate.</description></item><item><title>How to add accordion to your minimal theme</title><link>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/how-to-add-accordion-to-your-minimal-theme/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.doudmine.com/blog/how-to-add-accordion-to-your-minimal-theme/</guid><description>An &amp;ldquo;accordion&amp;rdquo; is a great way to display Products descriptions to your ecommerce store, since it allows the user to quickly and easily browse your Product informations without much scrolling. And luckily, it&amp;rsquo;s simple and easy to add one to your store! Let me show you how
From your Shopify admin, go to Online Store &amp;gt; Themes. Find the Minimal theme, and then click Actions &amp;gt; Duplicate. Find the theme that called Copy of Minimal then click Actions &amp;gt; Edit Code.</description></item></channel></rss>